You know where he is?
Yeah.
Should be easy then.
Let's go.
Ooh, yes, that's it.
That's it.
Oh, baby, I'm telling you, you gotta love
the Leaf Village.
The girls here are off the charts.
You're still playing the buffoon,
I see.
[chuckles]
Uhh, just doing a little research.
So, old man Homura and Koharu-sensei.
What could you two scholarly advisors want
with me?
Look at this.
Aah!
No, Lord Kazakage.
Ngh!
They've been dead for a while.
My guess, since before the Chunin exams.
I see now.
So that's what his game was.
Curse you, Orochimaru.
After the Kazakage was killed
Orochimaru, or Kabuto maybe,
assumed his identity.
We were careless.
Sarutobi...
You didn't think it would be
easy, did you?
Look who you were playing with
One of the most renowned ninja in
all the five great Shinobi nations
You did very well though
Two of the five are now out of the way
Shut your mouth!
I won't be patronized.
Do you understand me?
I'll kill you.
Forgive me.
I didn't wish to..
I'll grant you we didn't bring
down the village,
but let us not forget our other objective.
Sasuke
you've done it.
Your leash is around his neck.
[Orochimaru chuckles]
And all that it cost me were my arms and
the entirety of my jutsu.
If I'd only gotten hold of Itachi Uchiha
from the beginning
We wouldn't be in this mess.
But it's too late now.
That dream has died.
Itachi is stronger than I am.
That is why... I pulled myself
out of that organization.
The Sand Village has stated publicly that
Orochimaru was responsible for all of this.
At any rate, they've offered their
complete surrender to the Leaf Village.
So at the moment, their betrayal is a moot
point.
For now, we have no
choice but to accept their
surrender in order to shore
up our power in the region.
That's correct.
However, the strength of the Leaf Village
has just suffered an enormous blow.
As things now stand,
our top priority
is preparing for the onslaught
we believe will come.
We have no way of
knowing when one of the
surrounding nations
might try to make a play.
Therefore, until the village
has regained its strength
We've decided to gather the
top shinobi from each squad
And assemble an emergency executive
committee to handle the situation.
But first...
We need a strong and
trustworthy leader.
It is more than just Orochimaru.
It is the seed of a far greater struggle.
Look, guys, I don't know why you're going
to the trouble of explaining all this to me
But if you'll excuse me, I've got to
get back to w-
I think you'll be interested
in what our plans are.
This village needs the fifth Hokage
immediately.
And yesterday, at an
emergency meeting with
the Lord of the Land
of Fire, it was decided.
We chose you, Jiraiya.
Oh, I don't know.
It's not really up my alley.
It has been decided.
Besides, if one of the renowned
Sannin is not suited,
Then who else is?
If you're so set on a Sannin,
there is another.
Huh?
You're forgetting Tsunade.
There's little doubt that the
child has the capability
But it hardly matters.
No one even knows where she is.
I'm sure I can dig her up.
You don't have a problem with that,
do you?
But, uh...
Tsunade's got the brains for it.
More than a loafer like me does.
What do you say?
Very well, then.
We'll give it some thought.
But we'll send along
three members of the Anbu
Black Ops to accompany
you on your search.
You don't have to worry.
I'm not going to make a run for it.
Besides, your men will just get in the
way.
Although...
There is one guy I wouldn't mind having
along for the ride.
I've stumbled across a very interesting
little egg.
[wind howls]
Hey, guys.
You two seem to be getting along.
Huh!? Idiot.
Anko just asked me to pick up some rice
dumplings for her.
What are you doing here, aside from
catching up on your reading?
Ah, I need to buy something
to put on a grave.
Plus, I'm meeting somebody here.
I'm just waiting on Sasuke.
Hah! It's not like you to be
waiting on somebody.
Is it for Obito?
Obito?
Uh, yeah, kind of.
[glass thunks]
Kakashi, it's not like you to show up
early.
What gives?
Well, sometimes I do.
Let's eat somewhere else.
I don't have much of a sweet tooth.
Hmm. Is that so?
[woosh]
Mmm! [slurps]
Yeah, what happened there was...
I stuck it behind my headband because I
was so freaked out it was going to fall
out of my pants or something while I was
working out earlier this morning.
[chuckles]
Well, it all worked out in the end.
Now go on, eat up so you can do your best.
Huh?
You've got more training ahead of you,
don't you?
[chuckles]
You bet I do!
I'm going to work my butt off!
That's the spirit!
Here, have some more.
Hm?
That one there is on the house.
Dig in!
Oh man, thanks a bunch!
[chuckles]
Hey there, come on in.
I had to see it with my own eyes.
Hm?
It looks like you do eat nothing but
ramen, huh, short stuff?
Huh?
The pervy sage!
It's been a long time, Asuma, Kuranai.
The fact that you know
our names must mean
that you're a shinobi
formerly of this village.
[gasp]
Y-you're...
[bell jingles]
Heh.
Well, what do you know?
Itachi Uchiha.
Are these friends of yours, Itachi?
Well then...
I suppose I should introduce myself.
Hope we can get acquainted later.
The name's Kisame Hoshigaki.
Why should we wait till later,
When I can just wipe the
floor with you both now?
Boy, Itachi
It looks like they hate you as much
in this village as they do in mine.
We know who you are, Kisame.
We've heard all about you.
You hail from the Village of the Mist.
Suspected of espionage and the
murder of a feudal lord.
You're a rogue ninja from the Land of
Water, wanted in every nation.
You're a high-level S-rank criminal
listed prominently in the Bingo book.
This guy is getting on my nerves.
Can I kill him?
Well, I guess we're not going anywhere
without a fight.
Just try not to overdo it.
Your moves tend to stand out.
They're as good as dead.
[grunts]
I see.
Genjutsu.
He's bearing down with just the edge of
his sword.
His strength is unreal.
My massive blade, Sharkskin.
Hyah!
It doesn't slice.
It cuts you to ribbons!
It's about time, Kurenai.
Let's end this!
Genjutsu of that level
doesn't work on me.
He used a Genjutsu reflection?
[yells]
Kurenai!
I wouldn't be looking over there
If I were you.
You live up to your reputation.
However... [interrupted]
However, this is the end of the line.
For you, anyway.
What?
Water style.
[simultaneous]
Water Shark Bomb Jutsu!
He broke out the same jutsu that I did.
Not that I'm unhappy to see you,
but what are you doing here?
Well, you know, I asked you to take care
of those two earlier.
But I guess I got a little worried.
Kakashi.
It's you.
Those eyes haven't changed.
This one's a true heir of the Sharingan.
That means I've got to be ready for the
worst.
Well, well, what a surprise.
That's how you copied my jutsu.
So there really is someone besides Itachi
with those crazy eyes.
You're Kakashi, aren't you?
The copy ninja.
You can imagine my surprise.
I go to check out a couple of low-life
vagabonds in the tea house, and I find
none other than Itachi Uchiha
and Kisame Hoshigaki
The scourge of the
Hidden Mist Village.
How about that?
You know my name.
I'm honored.
I assume that bizarre
excuse for a sword is
one of the seven ninja
swordmen of the mist.
The one called Sharkskin?
Hahahahaha!
I heard that you and Zabuza
had it out a while back.
Yes, we did.
Ngh!
Go ahead.
I'd love to cut you to ribbons.
Kisame, stop it.
Huh?
If you take this man on, it won't be
without cost.
Furthermore, it will take
time, and the commotion
is liable to bring
more shinobi running.
Your way is inefficient and unnecessarily
risky.
Don't lose sight of our goal.
Let's hear it.
What is your goal exactly?
We're looking for something, and we know
it's here.
And what would that be?
My way is more...
efficient than Kisame's.
Ninja art, water style, water wall!
The speed of his jutsu is incredible.
I didn't even see a hand sign.
The shuriken in his hand were just a ruse
to distract me from his water style attack.
You're good.
You almost anticipated my moves.
Almost.
A shadow clone!
His speed is too great.
A water clone?
I guess my village should be honored he's
copied our jutsu so well.
Nice job, Kakashi.
Get back, Kurenai!
That one's the shadow clone.
Kakashi! Kurenai!
He just blew up his own shadow clone.
Are you alright?
Stay on your toes.
This guy was made chief of Anbu Black Ops
when he was only thirteen.
For someone who is not of the Uchiha clan,
you have mastered the Sharingan well.
However, not being one of us,
you lack our physical strength
And that's something
you can't copy.
He's right.
My body doesn't have the stamina.
Why is it that the Uchiha clan
is known by all,
And feared by all?
Huh?! It can't be.
Oh no.
Close your eyes!
Don't look at his eyes!
Listen, both of you.
Whatever happens, don't look.
If you meet his gaze, you're finished.
I'm gonna have to do this alone.
My Sharingan against his.
Indeed, your abilities are impressive.
They might even be enough to resist the
Mangekyou Sharingan.
However...
There is something they
can't defend against.
This special Sharingan jutsu called
Tsukuyomi.
Only someone with the Sharingan and
Kekkei Genkai can defeat me.
Sasuke...
I wonder how much of this someone without
the Kekkei Genkai can take.
In the Tsukuyomi...
[stabs] [grunts]
Time and space...
Even physical mass...
I control them all
Aah!
The next seventy-two hours will
be nothing but this.
Over and over...
[grunting in pain]
[heartbeat pounding]
[gasps]
Kakashi, what is it?
Can we open our eyes now?
No.
Not yet.
What just happened?
One second the guy's talking and the next
second you hit the ground!
Three days in that world.
Less than a moment passed in this one.
Why not just kill me?
If he wanted to, he could.
Hmm. After all that, the fool's
spirit is still intact.
Meanwhile, you've risked
overusing those eyes of yours.
You know that's dangerous.
This... thing you've come for...
is it Sasuke?
No.
The legacy of the Fourth Hokage.
What's he talking about?
What's he after?
[looks super cool]
Naruto...
It's been a long time, Jiraiya.
How many years since you've
even seen the village?
Kakashi...
I'll train Naruto from now on.
The Third Hokage was wise to place the boy
under your supervision.
He's been well looked after.
But even someone of your
remarkable abilities
might not be enough to get him ready.
Ready?
What are you talking about?
I've been keeping a close
watch on Orochimaru all
this time ever since the
day he left the village.
It was clear that he meant
to come back someday, and it
was important to know what
he was planning in the meantime.
For many years, I observed his movements.
But then...
What?
He became part of an organization.
What organization?
What's its purpose?
No one really knows for sure
But it's a roving gang of
nine like-minded shinobi who
call themselves the Akatsuki.
At first, they stuck to small-scale
cloak-and-dagger stuff.
Nothing dramatic.
But you knew something big was coming,
considering who they are.
These are not small-timers.
Almost everyone in the
organization is listed in
the bingo book as an
S-class criminal deviant.
For instance
That guy Itachi's one of them.
When nine shinobi
like that get together,
it's not because they
want to do charity work.
Recently, the groups started splitting up.
Orochimaru went off on his own,
while others paired up and dispersed
through different areas, searching
for new jutsu to master.
And other things as well.
And one of these things they're looking
for is the nine-tailed fox?
It's only a... possibility.
Kakashi.
Sooner or later, Naruto must
learn that because of what
he is, he'll have to live
his life watching his back.
That's the boy's destiny.
For now, focus on Sasuke.
It's up to you to teach him how to use his
Sharingan.
And I'll keep an eye on Naruto.
Leave his training to me.
The nine-tailed spirit inside Naruto.
That's what you're after?
You're not the only ones, are you?
There are seven more of you out there.
Searching... hunting...
I know all about you.
You call yourselves the Akatsuki,
right?
Akatsuki?
Kisame.
We'll take Kakashi with us.
But we don't need the others.
Get rid of them.
Severe Leaf Hurricane!
Well, who have we here?
The Leaf Village's fiercest beast of
battle.
I'm Might Guy!
You're Might Guy, huh?
Mighty stupid looking guy.
Don't underestimate him.
It's him.
Itachi.
What they must have put him through...
Close your eyes.
Don't look at Itachi.
You'll get caught in his jutsu.
Relax.
I know what I'm doing.
After spending this much time
training to fight Kakashi,
I know all about Sharingan.
Alright, both of you.
Open your eyes, now.
But... if we...
Don't worry, just
don't look in his eyes.
That's the key to fighting an opponent
who's using Sharingan.
Focus on his feet.
You can read what he's gonna do from his
feet.
Alright, but that trick sounds a lot
easier said than done.
We haven't had all your training.
We're not you, Guy.
True.
It takes skill to anticipate an opponent's
moves merely from watching his feet.
But I don't have time to teach you now.
You'll just have to do your best.
So what do we do?
Kurenai, get Kakashi to the medical corp.
Asuma, you'll be my backup.
Got it.
Alright.
I sent word for the Anbu Black Ops,
but until they get here, we hold them off.
Just you and me.
Interesting.
I'll give you credit for guts.
No, Kisame.
We're pulling out.
We're not here to fight a full-scale
battle.
Tempting as it may be, it's not the way to
do this.
Let's go.
That's too bad.
It was just getting fun.
They don't know how lucky they are.
What?
Agh, No way!
How come I get stuck
tagging along with you while
you do research for another
one of your pervy books?
Look, kid.
I can assure you this isn't just another
research trip.
There's a woman I have to find.
A very remarkable woman.
Well, count me out, old man.
I don't have time to help you find a
girlfriend.
I've got to get busy with my training.
What training?
It's time Kakashi Sensei taught me
something new, like that Chidori thing.
Why does he always play favorites with
Sasuke?
I see.
Hmm.
You'd just be wasting your time.
Chidori's not really your style.
And besides that, kid, the woman we're
looking for is really beautiful.
I mean gorgeous.
Like I care.
Look, pervy sage, who do you think you're
talking to?
I'm not some dumb kid you can fool with
lame excuses.
I'm not going!
Okay, fine. Suit yourself.
And I could have taught you jutsu that
made Chidori look like kid stuff.
Maybe I'll just... see if Sasuke wants to
come.
Right! When do we leave?
I'll go pack my bag.
Stay right there, pervy sage.
I'll be right back. Don't move!
What a knucklehead.
Still, you can't help liking him.
All right, I'm ready.
Well, come on, pervy sage!
I'm on pins and needles.
What's this new jutsu you're going to
teach me?
The last time around it was a walk on
water jutsu.
Ooh, is it walking through fire?
Or wait, maybe walking on air.
Ah, come on, pervy sage.
Let's hear it already.
All right, enough with the pervy sage
already.
You have no idea how amazing a guy I am,
do you?
Huh? What, amazingly pervy?
Gah!? You!
All right, listen up!
The Toad Sage is only my cover.
Allow me to reveal my true identity.
From the north to the
south, and the east to the
west, not even the spirits
can defeat this Sannin.
The white-maned Toad Charmer!
A red-hot ninja who strikes fear in the
hearts of men!
Master Jiraiya! Haha!
Yes! I'm speaking of none other than
myself!
Hahahahahahaha!
Uh-huh.
Uh, Atafuku Town.
That's ten kilometers from here.
No, it's OH-tofuku Town.
Ohh!
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait a second!
Pervy Sage!
Look, kid, I told you already,
it's Jiraiya.
Come on!
So, the fact that such a
bigwig pervy sage chose me
as his traveling companion
must mean something, right?
I must be a potential genius in the
making!
Aw man, it's just like I always thought!
Gyahaha!
Come on, come on, come on!
Why'd you choose me, huh?
Well, the truth is, kid,
a long time ago, the
fourth Hokage used
to be a disciple of mine.
Huh?
And you bear such a striking resemblance
to the fourth that it's almost laughable.
Sorry, that's the only reason I got for
you.
So wait...
I'm like the fourth?
Holy crap!
Aah!
That's awesome!
Hahahaha!
What's up with you?
Oh man!
[giggles]
If I'm like the fourth Hokage, that means I
possess the same level of genius he did!
I'm on my way to Hokage after all!
Woohoo! Hahahaha!
Huh! Hah! Hoo!
Ah, yippee!
Huh?
Mh?
Aah! No, no, no!
Wait!
Ah, no!
I just stepped in some dog doo!
[sighs]
[panting]
I wasn't...
I wasn't able to do anything.
I don't ever want to have to see that
again.
Watching all my best friends falling right
in front of me.
No matter what happens!
I swear I'm going to protect you!
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto just gets stronger and stronger.
Compared to him, I...
Raaaaaagh!
No I'm pretty certain you could go toe-to-toe
with him, though I'm not sure I could.
He's on a whole other level.
Yeah... If we faced each other,
both of us would be killed.
A rather unappealing outcome.
Even if there were more of us,
the result would remain the same.
Never thought I'd have to go up against
one of the legendary Sanin.
If we fight him, then both
the Uchiha clan
and the Seven Swordsmen
of the Mist
Will have their names dragged
through the mud.
True.
But still...
Even the strongest of opponents
Always has a weakness.
They're trouble.
But from the look of things, it doesn't
appear they've found Naruto yet.
That's what's crazy.
It doesn't add up.
I mean, they had already infiltrated the
village.
It should be easy for them to find Naruto
around here.
Besides, Itachi knows
Naruto's face already.
Shh!
Kakashi!
Why is Kakashi asleep?
And why is this room full of Jonin?
What are you doing?
What the hell is going on here?
Uh, not much, really.
Hey! is it true that Itachi has returned?
And that he's come here to get Naruto?
Uh... ohh..
Idiot.
Ah, why does this always
have to happen!?
So he's come back to
the village, huh?
And he's after Naruto?
What does this mean?
If Naruto gets caught,
He's dead!
I won't let that happen!
Old man! Naruto stopped
in here today!
Do you know where he went after he left?
Oh, sure. Naruto.
That's right, let me see now.
He met Master Jiraiya here around noon.
They had a little bit of ramen, then they
said they were heading off somewhere.
Where to?
Hmm...
Now that I think of it,
I believe he mentioned
that outpost town a ways
out from the village. Yeah.
And then he set out with Master Jiraiya.
Jiraiya?
Yeah, Jiraiya.
He's one of the legendary Sannin!
Now, if you want to find
him, you're looking for
a great big old fellow
with a head of white hair.
A big guy.
White hair.
Get your candy here!
Naruto!
Huh?
We're gonna crash here tonight.
What?
But why?
I can still walk.
A disciple should always obey his master.
Look, I just want to learn some jutsu,
okay?
Yeah, no kidding, that's what make you a
disciple.
Hmm?
Hm?
[magical harp playing]
[giggling]
Aah! Naruto!
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah!
Here's the room key.
I want you to go right
up to the room, train for a
little, work on your chakra,
then get to bed, okay?
Haha!
Wha!?
So I suppose you're gonna tell me it's
time for the grown-ups to play now,
Is that the vibe here, you big perv?
That outpost town isn't that far off.
Oh man, every single time I'm with that
pervy sage, I always end up getting shafted.
This is it.
Get your candy here, get your candy!
Guess I'll just have to go door to door.
Is there a dopey looking blonde kid about
my age staying here now?
He's traveling through the city with a big
guy with white hair?
White hair, you say?
Are they here?
Did I see someone like that at the shift
change?
I wonder.
This is kind of a bitter drink,
can you handle it?
Okay, bottoms up!
Oh yeah!
A blonde kid and a white-haired old man.
So they're here then?
What room number?
Let's see now.
That would be room number one on the
second floor at the end of the hall.
Huh?
[knocking at door]
[knocking continues]
Ah, what now?
Are you telling me she dumped you already?
I heard you the first time!
Okay, hold on, let me just unlock it.
Naruto!
You're not...
[eerie music]
Sasuke?
No... who is he?
The same Sharingan as Sasuke's.
Huh. Hard to believe that such
a child carries a nine-tailed fox.
How does this guy know about the
nine-tailed fox?
Naruto, you're coming with us.
It's him!
He's here!
Why don't we take a walk?
These guys look like the real deal.
Hey, Itachi.
It'll be a pain in the neck if this kid
makes a run for it.
Maybe I oughta... chop off a leg,
just in case.
Say what?
Right.
It's been a long time, hm?
Sasuke.
Itachi.
Uchiha.
I hope you're ready...
To die!
Well, the Sharingan.
Itachi, Who is this kid?
He's my younger brother.
That's strange, cause
the way I heard it, the
whole Uchiha clan
was wiped out... by you.
This is who he was talking about.
The one he wanted to kill.
It's just as you said, brother.
I've fostered my hatred for you.
All this time, I've lived my life for one
single purpose.
To kill you!
It ends here!
[yells]
[bone breaks]
[screams]
Sasuke!
Damn!
Forget the legs.
Maybe I oughta start off with those arms
of his.
Master Jiraiya.
I know he's the one you're really after.
You're right.
Naruto is the prize that the Akatsuki are
after.
And we will have him.
Huh?
No way you're getting Naruto.
We'll see about that.
Actually, this is all very convenient.
I can eliminate you both at the same time.
Stay out of this!
The only one...
Who's going to eliminate him...
Is me!
Go away.
You don't interest me at the moment.
Sasuke, no!
Why you lousy!
No, Naruto!
Don't butt in!
Mind your own business!
Just back off!
This fight is mine!
Of course.
Revenge.
And now, finally!
[coughs]
All these years... nothing has changed.
How can it be?
I've trained for so long... just to kill
him... for so long.
What have I been doing all these years?
Was it... was it all for this?
You're weak, Sasuke.
And for the next 24 hours...
Relive that day.
That does it! I'm
through standing around!
Hraaaah!
Ninja Art.
Toadmouth Trap.
Too bad for you, Itachi... Kisame.
You've both just been swallowed by the
Mountain Toad.
This Toad has a sensitive digestive tract,
so don't upset him.
It must be humbling to know that you've
been reduced to Toad bait.
You're still too weak.
You don't have enough hate.
You never will.
Kisame, come.
Stop!
He's getting away!
A ninja hasn't been born yet who can
survive this powerful stomach.
Huh?
Hey!
Pervy Sage!
What the heck happened?
They both got away!
He did the impossible.
He broke through the wall.
So we just run away again?
We do a lot of that.
There's no rush for now. We'll
get Naruto when the time is right.
Besides, I felt it wise
for us to find some
place to rest for a while
and recharge my powers.
On top of Tsukuyomi,
to have to use Amatarasu
as well... It was more
exhausting than I thought.
What is this stuff anyway?
Some kind of black fire?
Stay away from it!
Ahh!
How did they do it?
What did they use to escape?
And these black flames?
To burn the stone toad when it has the
power to spit fire itself?
That is strong jutsu indeed.
Huh?
There.
Sealing jutsu!
Fire seal now!
Alright.
Well that takes care of that for the time
being.
Now for Sasuke.
Sasuke!
What did he do to him?
DYNAMIC
Guy?
ENTRY!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha...
Oh!
Heheh... I-I guess I was
a little over enthusiastic, uh
You see, I... I was trying to hurry and I
couldn't see very clearly.
Ha ha ha ha ha! Ehh...
Using my headband to peer into the
opening, all I could see were two sinister
figures, so... I'm gonna
put an end to this right now!
Do you know what?
If this is your way of saying sorry,
it stinks!
I'm sorry, but it was just a simple
misunderstanding.
Simple-minded's more like it.
But never mind that now.
We've got to get Sasuke to the medical
corps at once.
Right.
He's badly beaten up.
His arm is broken.
And he's been knocked out by whatever
jutsu that was that Itachi used on him.
Could it be the same thing he used on
Kakashi?
Pervy Sage!
Sasuke is gonna be alright though,
isn't he?
Physically, yes.
But I am worried about what may have been
done to his mind.
What the heck?
What did Sasuke ever do to deserve this?
Okay, Pervy Sage.
It's time for a new game plan.
Starting right now!
I admit, I let those goons scare me a
little.
But that's over.
No more running!
After all, it's me they're after,
right?
Well, okay then!
It's time I give them what they want!
Hmph.
Nice speech, kid.
But I'm afraid you wouldn't stand a chance
against them.
You're not in the same league.
What would have happened if I hadn't shown
up just now, huh?
It took all I had to get them away from
you.
Is that right?
So what are you suggesting?
That we just do nothing?
Sit here waiting for them to hit us again?
What kind of strategy is that?
Just be quiet!
You haven't earned the right.
I'm sorry, Guy.
I wanted to let Sasuke fight his own
fight.
I see now I should have intervened sooner.
This is obviously the same sort of jutsu
that Kakashi was hit with.
We don't know when he'll come out of it.
What? Kakashi-sensei?
There's nothing worse than
seeing your students fall in battle.
It's like losing little pieces of your
soul.
What we need is a supreme medical specialist,
a master of healing arts, and soon.
You're right.
And the woman you're talking about is the
one we've come to find.
Huh?
The woman?
You don't mean...
Hm-hm.
Aaaahhhhh!
Wha- what are you going
to do with all that cash?
Yes, that's exactly who I mean.
Another of the legendary Sannin,
the queen of slugs and elixirs.
Take a good look, Shizune.
The losing streak is over.
Our luck is about to change!
The gambling fool and
mistress of the healing arts...
Lady Tsunade!
All right, guy.
We'll leave Sasuke in your hands.
Master Jiraiya.
Hm?
Find the Lady Tsunade.
Bring her back to us.
Don't worry, you can count on us!
We'll have her back in the village in no
time!
Naruto, nothing impresses me more than
guts, kid.
Come here, let me give you this.
Hm?
Lee got stronger with this.
Really? What?
What is it?
Check it out!
[groans]
It's breathable, retains
moisture, and offers complete
complete freedom of movement
all in one sweet... package.
If you wear it while you train,
you'll notice a difference immediately.
They really grow on you.
Pretty soon, you'll be wearing them all
the time, just like Lee.
I've got a bit of a thing for them myself.
Oh, man!
Ugh, If you're gonna walk
around carrying that thing,
you oughta pack a hand
mirror or two, you idiot.
Pretty cool, huh?
Don't even think about it.
I mean, look at that guy.
Huh?
I know that he's the one you're really
after.
You're right.
Naruto is the prize that the Akatsuki are
after.
And we will have him.
Hm.
What's up?
So, Pervy Sage.
What exactly do those guys want with me,
anyway?
Hm...
Come on out with it, Pervy Sage.
You know, don't you?
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's not you they want.
It's what's inside of you.
What the hell is this thing, anyway?
Some horrible demon that terrorized the
Leaf Village.
That's why everyone's so afraid of it,
right?
So why do these guys want it so bad?
The nine-tailed fox has appeared in times
of consequence all through the ages,
a ghastly spirit destroying all that lays
in its path.
As powerful as any act of nature,
men trembled before it.
As for what they would
want with that malicious
monstrosity, that's a hard
question to answer, Naruto.
I honestly can't say.
I suppose with the Nine
Tails sealed up inside you, they
might be thinking of somehow
seizing control of that power.
Bending it to their will.
It's a bitter pill to swallow knowing that
those two will be after you now.
But that is your fate.
Not to worry though, after all you will
have me around.
Oh well, I'll just have to hurry up and
get stronger.
No other choice.
Hm?
Alright!
Let's find the Tsunade woman
you're talking about, so she
can fix up Sasuke and we get
down to some serious training!
This kid's got a one-track mind.
Ayiee!
This place has the highest minimum in
town!
Don't get your panties in a bunch.
Let's do this.
Oh, wait for me!
Hmm...
What now?
This beautiful woman that you've got us
out here scouting around for.
Is she the Tsunade that you mentioned?
Hey! Not bad, kid.
You're pretty sharp, aren't you?
Why? What's on your mind then?
Well, you said she was one of the three
legendary Sannin.
The same as you, right, Pervy Sage?
That's right.
What's your point already?
How old is she?
Same age as me.
Ugh, she's ancient.
Ayieee!
Hm?
Wait, she's...
Here's all my cash.
You think I could get some chips?
She's going all in!
Oink!
Looks like a pretty big spender.
Who is this broad?
You're kidding. You
never heard of her?
She's the one with the crazy nickname.
Nickname?
So, what's this Tsunade lady like,
anyway?
Ah, curious, are you?
Yeah.
What can I tell you?
Well, for one thing, she's kind of
unpleasant.
Plus, I guess there's
the fact that she's known
far and wide as a
die-hard gambler and all.
Great!
This should be a piece of cake,
then, if she's as famous as all that.
Oh, she's famous, all right.
You might even call her Legendary.
So, ah, what's this crazy nickname she's
got?
The Legendary.
Legendary... Huh?
Ha ha ha ha ha... Ha ha
ha ha ha... Ha ha ha ha ha...
Why are they all laughing?
Oink oink...
The Legendary...
Sucker!
But as legendary a
sucker as she may be
I doubt she's going
to be all that easy to find.
Why? What makes you say that?
She's not the type to grow old gracefully.
Probably using some kind of jutsu to mask
her appearance.
She's actually fifty
years old, but I'm sure
she'll look more like
she did in her twenties.
Huh?
That's not all.
The word on the wind I hear of late is she
started transforming on the fly,
going from her teens to
her thirties or forties, all so
she can cut out on any
moneylender she's in too deep with.
That's awful!
Aw man, she sounds like a charmer!
Yeah, well, Tsunade's always loved
gambling more than anything.
It's too bad she never had any luck.
Or skill, for that matter.
She was made a sucker so many times the
name just stuck with her.
But then she would just borrow money and
skip out on her debts.
Ah, it brings me back, I tell ya.
Hey, we don't have time for nostalgia!
What?
Come on!
Do you have a plan for finding her or
what?
Not exactly.
We might have a little
work ahead of us, but
I'm sure you and I'll
come up with something.
So you don't even have the slightest idea
how long this is gonna take, do you?
Not a minute will be wasted.
Huh?
All our time on the road will be devoted
solely to you.
To me?
We've gotta get you stronger.
Time to train!
Okay!
Ah! Wait, wait, wait,
wait wait!
Hold on a second!
Look, I already told you, I'm not having
that!
I don't want to be seen
walking around with
someone wearing that,
that, that, that thing!
Come on, Pervy Sage!
What are we waiting for?
Let's start my training already!
All right, don't get ahead of yourself
now.
I have to train you while we gather
information on Tsunade.
Otherwise, it's not going to mean anything
to you.
Huh? Gather information?
In this town!
Whoa!
[overlapping voices]
Wait up!
Hurry, hurry!
Ah, man, this is gonna be great!
I've never seen anything like this before
in my life!
Downtime is important, so have a little
fun before we start your training.
This festival will be going on for a
while.
We'll hunker down here till it's over.
And then we'll start your training here,
too.
All right!
Oh, baby!
That is one fat frog you got!
You're filthy rich!
Yeah, I've got a pretty big stash!
I've been saving up bit by
bit from my missions!
Catch you later!
Stop right there, Naruto!
Huh?
I'm going to hold onto your wallet for
you.
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?
Here.
You can have this much to spend.
What?
Only 300?
I don't want to hear it!
Honoring the shinobi's three prohibitions
is the duty of any upstanding ninja!
Three prohibitions?
What are you talking about?
You're kidding!
Don't you know?
The three prohibitions
are a trio of temptations
that will bring a
shinobi to his ruin!
Those three prohibitions are alcohol,
pretty women, and worst of all, money.
Yeah, well, none of those things really
apply to me all that much, so we're cool.
I mean, I'm underage, so I can't drink
yet.
I don't really get the whole woman thing.
And I worked so hard to
save all that money that
I really don't feel like
spending a ton of it.
You little fool!
Don't take money lightly!
Once you start spending, you'll never
stop!
Money possesses a frightful power.
This woman, Tsunade,
that we're searching for
has ruined herself
with the pursuit of it.
Pretty big talk coming from someone so
addicted to the ladies.
I'm gonna go see if I can gather some
information.
Here, I want you to hold onto my bag for
me, okay?
If you happen to get lost
somehow, you can always
rely on my tracker toad
to sniff out my scent.
Gotta keep reminding myself he's still
just a kid.
Last one!
Bullseye!
Right on target!
Well, that shuriken training wasn't for
nothing.
Huh?
Aaaaaaah!
Man, kid, you stink!
Huh. Yeah, we'll see.
Get a load of this.
Not so fast.
What?
Mm-mm-mm.
Mmh?
Attention, Shinobi.
Ninjutsu strictly forbidden?
Oh. Haha.. Hehe...
Thank you.
Careful, kid. You shouldn't
walk around with that mask on.
Ow!
Hmm?
Hey...
it's the Pervy Sage's checkbook.
One... ten... one hundred...
L-Look at all those zeros!
Geez!
He should be treating me right now if he's
this loaded for crying out loud!
Cheap old geezer!
Not much left.
One more stand and that'll be it for the
day.
We've gotta get you stronger.
Time to train!
Hmph.
Hey, how's it going?
I'd like to get two grilled squid,
please.
Oh, and, uh, make one of those big enough
for a grown-up.
Okay, coming up.
Got sent in a squid run, huh?
Tell you what, I'll throw in the kid's
size for free.
Thanks a lot, mister!
You're the man!
Oh, you think so, huh?
Well, you're getting half price on that
other squid, too.
Wow! Thanks!
Good grief.
Where did he run off to?
Yahaha haha!
Huh?
Was that Pervy Sage?
Hmm?
Ha ha ha!
What can I say?
I love the ladies!
Oh. Hey, kid.
Had your fill of the festival already,
huh?
[slurps]
I need a refresher!
What were those prohibitions of yours
again?
What's the matter with you?
You're breaking all three in
one go, you dirty...
Uh... Wait! Naruto!
Wait, schmait! I can't believe
you squandered all my
Naruto stop!
I'll get it all back, I promise!
hard earned savings!
I'm sorry! Please!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Not the face! Ouch!
Lousy good-for-nothing!
Look at my froggy!
It's flat as a pancake!
Watch it!
Look what you did, you little punk!
Huh?
You stained the boss's brand-new designer
suit, you street rat!
You're paying for that!
A hundred thousand large!
What? You're telling me that
suit cost a hundred thousand?!
That seems a little bit
of a stretch, fellas
You expect us to believe that monkey suit
is worth a hundred thousand?
You looking for trouble, old man?
You'll shut your yap if you know it's good
for you.
The boss used to be a Chunin from the
hidden village of the stones!
The legendary dark ninja, feared across
the land!
Ah!
This I gotta hear!
The legendary what now?
You're asking for it, pal!
Just keep pushing!
Naruto?
Huh?
This is perfect timing.
I have a new jutsu I want to show you.
Now, pay attention.
Enough already!
That was awesome!
And I was holding back.
Oh, you guys are hardly worth the trouble.
Wait a minute!
You're... the legendary...
Sorry about that. I guess we
kind of messed up your stand.
Here!
This should cover it.
Ah! Thanks a lot!
Now then, my good man.
I'd like to buy every balloon you've got,
including water balloons.
How's that sound?
Fine by me, I guess.
... ...
That was no ordinary hand move.
What the heck kind of jutsu was that?
Naruto!
Huh?
Let's get going.
Time for you to train.
Yes, sir!
Alright!
It's finally time to get down to business!
Here you go. Have
a water balloon.
Huh? What the heck is this for?
Just think about it.
You saw the jutsu I performed,
right?
Uh-huh.
And how would you describe it?
Hmm...
You sent that guy spinning like a
pinwheel.
Ah, he's not quite getting it.
But I've got an idea.
Good! Spinning!
There you go!
He's spinning the water in that balloon
without even moving his hand!
Whoa!
With the tree-climbing exercise,
you learn to gather and maintain chakra.
With the water-walking exercise, you
learn to release a steady amount of it.
Both of these you've mastered,
correct?
With the water-balloon exercise,
you'll learn to create a stream of chakra.
Spinning it, as you so aptly put it.
I'm supposed to create a stream of chakra?
Don't worry. I'll go into more
detail on how the jutsu works
once you've gotten
a handle of the basics.
First, gather the chakra in your hand
using the tree-climbing technique.
Then, release a steady stream of it using
the walk-on-water technique.
And finally, use the chakra to push and
churn the water inside of the balloon.
Wait a second! I get it!
So what you're aiming
for then is to spin the
water inside the balloon
until it eventually pops!
Atta boy! You're starting
to catch on quicker!
Okay! We'll train until
the sun goes down!
Yes, sir!
Hah.
Huh.
I wonder if Naruto's got what it takes.
I can't wait to see what happens.
What's cooking, good-looking?
Are you the guy we've heard about?
The one doing research on pretty girls?
Yeah! That's right,
you've heard of me?
We'd be glad to help you with your
research.
Buy us dinner, we'll stamp your card.
When the card's full, we'll tell you
everything.
Woo-hoo! Sounds like fun!
What's your name, sweetie?
Uh-uh. Dinner first.
Leave him alone now, Whiskers.
Come on down.
Excuse me.
Which way's the restroom?
Okay! Here we go, Naruto!
You're gonna nail this thing today!
Come on and burst, you stupid balloon!
Nothing!
What do I gotta do?
I just love your hair, Jiraiya.
Is that its real color?
Hahahaha!
Darling, everything about me is real!
Aaaaah!
Give me a break!
It's been three
days! And nothing!
It stretches, but it won't burst!
Rotating it to the left doesn't make any
difference!
That dang pervy sage knows something I
don't!
But what?
Hahahaha!
Man, oh man!
I just love this town!
Hahahaha!
What the...
Yuck!
He could seriously use some mouthwash!
Okay! Gotta build
up my strength!
Huh?
Wha... What's wrong with me?
Come on!
Great! Now I'm having
a nervous breakdown!
That's all I need!
With a little effort, even a slow learner
can get this one.
I know that you can do it.
He said there were no complicated hand
signs to learn.
Huh? Hey! Leave that alone!
It's not a toy!
That's it!
Rise and shine, pervy sage!
Come on! Drag those
old bones out of bed!
Oh... good.
Since you're here, bring me some water,
would ya?
Some water?
Hmph!
Yuck!
So, that's the first phase of training.
What's next?
Oh, you did it, huh?
Would you mind giving me a little
demonstration?
Watch carefully!
Keep your eyes on the balloon!
Hnggggg...
Interesting...
Haa!
There, old man!
What'd you think of that, huh?
[snoring]
Wha... huh... you...
Gaaaaaah!
Sorry about that. I've just
been working day and night.
You know, doing research.
Research, huh?
Is that what you call it?
[slurps]
Gotta hand it to him.
He found a way to do it.
By steadying it with his left hand and
applying chakra with his right.
It's a weird idea, but then, hey,
he's a weird kid.
And weird isn't necessarily bad.
[chuckles]
Looks like you did
it. Good for you.
I guess that little tip I gave you helped
out after all.
[meow]
Actually, I've really got him to thank.
Huh?
I was watching this guy play around with
my balloon, and I got a brilliant idea.
See, he kept knocking it back and forth,
which meant the water inside must be going
back and forth, too, in different
directions.
That's when it came to me!
And what would that be, exactly?
I thought back to when you were showing me
what to do that first time.
I remembered how bumpy the surface of the
balloon got, like it was boiling.
My problem was, I was making the water
rotate, but in only one direction.
That's why my balloon was smooth,
not bumpy like yours.
If it was gonna burst, I had
to get the water spinning
in a bunch of different
directions, bumping into itself.
So... Once I finally figured
that part out, the rest was easy!
Well, he still may not be capable of
executing it with only one hand,
but he found a way, and it works.
What can I say? I rule, huh?
Okay, then.
You have successfully completed the first
step.
All right!
Here, let me show it to you one more time.
Wanna see it again?
He's used up a lot of chakra.
Can his chakra network withstand the
strain?
And it only gets harder from here.
All right, then.
You ready to proceed to the second step
now?
Yeah!
Enough with the kid stuff!
What's next, weapons,
or... There you go.
Huh?
A rubber ball, hey!
Ah, come on, you're kidding me,
right?
Let's see if you can pop this one.
And let me tell you, it's a lot harder
than a water balloon.
This is hard.
The first element is rotation.
The second element is force.
But this object is solid.
There's no water
inside, so it's far more
difficult to exert your
chakra rotation on it.
Yeah, I can see that.
I'll leave it to you to figure out.
I'll have to come up with something new
for this one.
And in the meanwhile, I better get back to
my research.
Hey, Pervy Sage, don't go away again!
Come on, stay and help me with my
training!
Don't leave me out here by myself!
Stop whining!
There's one part of this process you don't
seem to understand.
I said I'd be your teacher, not your
father or your best friend.
I'm not here to hold your hand.
You have to do this by yourself,
or not at all.
Stop being a child and learn how to stand
on your own two feet like a shinobi.
Uh, all right, I will.
I was just hoping before you go, you
could just show it to me one more time?
Pay me.
Get out of here, you greedy old skirt
chaser!
You're one to talk about growing up and
acting like a shinobi!
Why don't you act like a shinobi instead
of a pervy old bag of bones?!
Just like he said, this is way more
difficult than the water balloon!
My arms and hands are killing me!
Don't know how much more they can take!
How many days?
Doing the same thing over and over?
It's one of the master rank ninjutsu.
Stop whining.
I'm not holding your hand.
You have to do this yourself or not at
all.
Alright.
Hey, Naruto.
What are you doing here, pervy sage?
I want you to hop into town and grab me
some lunch.
Huh?
Why do I have to?
I'm your teacher, and a student is always
obliged to obey his teacher.
Grr...
Here you go, son.
Thanks... Thanks a lot.
I'm your teacher.
Some teacher.
What's he taught me?
Nothing.
I want one of those, Dad. Can I?
Huh?
The frozen fruit on a stick.
Please?
There you go.
Aww. I'm big now!
I can eat the whole thing myself!
No, we'll share.
Besides, what would your mother say if I
let you spoil your supper?
Okay.
Say, I was wondering...
Hm?
Well, um, maybe you could stick around for
a while today?
Help me train?
Sorry, no time.
I've got to go into town
and keep an appointment
with someone
who's helping me with my research.
It's up to you to figure out by yourself,
Naruto.
Otherwise, there's no
point in even learning it
for all the good it will do you.
I thought I made it clear three weeks ago.
Stop acting like a helpless child.
You're a ninja.
Haha!
Oh, sure, of course.
Don't worry about me.
I understand!
Forget about it. I was
just asking, that's all.
Go on and do whatever you have to do,
Pervy Sage.
No, you did that?
I don't think I believe you.
Hey! It's true!
Jiraiya is no liar!
[laughter]
[laughing stops suddenly]
Ah jeez, what's the use?
It won't pop no matter how hard I try.
I'm just wasting my time, burning up
chakra for no good reason.
And this pain...
The more I try to increase the flow,
the more it hurts.
But I have to.
I have to give it all I've got,
or it'll never pop.
But what if all I've got isn't enough?
That's it!
If I can work through the
pain to generate more chakra,
and then push it right to
the limit of what I can endure...
Not enough yet!
Not yet!
Still not enough!
Now!
Yeah, I've got it!
I've got it!
Well, well.
We seem to have made progress.
Hm?
Yeah, but I only made it spring a leak,
not burst like you did.
Boy, you're getting awfully picky all of a
sudden.
Here, want one?
You've come far, and all on your own.
It's delicious!
So, you ready to try a little experiment?
Sure! What?
Give me your right hand.
Hm?
Hehehe...
Uh, what is it?
Hm?
Take a look.
Hm? It's the same mark!
I don't get it, how's this supposed to
help?
You're the kind of kid
who got yelled at in the
Academy for a lack of
concentration, aren't ya?
I don't see what that has to do with this.
Look at this piece of paper.
Huh?
I've seen it.
All right.
Now, if you will, give it a second look.
Huh?
What am I looking at?
Well, I don't think it's going to help a
whole lot if I explain too much right away.
But the first time you
looked at this paper, your
eyes just glanced at the
whole thing, am I right?
Probably.
And what about the second time you looked?
Most likely the point in the middle?
Huh?
Any time that a person's
eyes gaze on a blank
sheet of paper, they
don't focus where to look.
The eyes just wander the page.
But if you put even a dot on it,
the mind is drawn there.
You're then concentrating on a single
point.
And with that focus comes spiritual
stability.
Letting you tap into unimaginable power.
Hmm...
When you finally broke open the hole in
the rubber ball, I'm sure you must have
been trying desperately to gather up the
chakra you needed in the palm of your hand.
Yeah, that's right!
When you concentrate, you draw out power.
But without some sort of target,
concentration can be difficult.
Hence that mark.
Now listen, Naruto.
From now on, when you're
storing a power in your right
hand, make sure that you
concentrate only on that mark.
Concentrate...
Alright!
I guess I can handle that!
I'm here, Sasuke.
Gyah!
My arms!
Lord Orochimaru, are you okay?
Quick! Your medicine!
[sighs] I just got back.
Now I have to clean the room.
Please be sure to take your medicine,
will you?
That medicine will do nothing for me,
you simpleton!
But I made it specifically for you.
It should ease your pain.
At least a little.
This burning in my arms... I never
imagined the suffering would be this great!
It was Sarutobi, after all.
The third Hokage.
This was his final curse.
Enough of your prattling!
Tell me, have you found the one I seek?
Yes.
The trail led to a place called
Tanzaku town.
Tanzaku town...
I see... Lest you forget.
Your opponent's one of the legendary
Sannin.
This isn't going to be easy.
[chuckles]
The best medicines are always bitter.
Gaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!
Concentrate!
I don't think that's gonna cut it.
It has to pop!
Concentrate!
Hi there! I was hoping you
could help me with something.
Dang it!
Concentrate!
It's no use.
I thought I knew what concentration was.
[sighs]
Guh! [gasps] Aaaaaahhhh!
Curse you, Sarutobi!
Nngaaaaaah!
[panting]
All right, then.
I gotta go back and scrounge up some more
information.
What? Come on,
you just got here!
Sorry, kid, but I don't have any time to
waste.
Hey! That's it?
Not even a soulful little game of catch
between a pupil and his master?
You lousy bum!
Hmm?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha haa!
Strike!
There you go, kid.
Game over.
Nya ha ha ha ha ha ha!
See you around, sport!
Hmph!
Who needs that pervy sage?
I'll just dig in and work this out on my
own.
There's no other way, Naruto.
This training you must do alone.
You can attain the level
of the fourth Hokage
someday, but you must
grab it on your own.
Hmm...
Nope, never laid eyes on her.
Ah, I see.
Sorry to have been any trouble.
I know who you're talking about.
Hmm?
And I can tell you where she is right now,
too.
How about a drink, friend?
Heh. That's all right, thanks.
I made out like a bandit not too long ago.
Thanks to the lady.
Yes!
You are indeed the legendary sucker!
Hmm... She lost again, did she?
Lovely.
Her losses were really piling up, so
she went looking for a change of scenery.
Where to?
Seven... Seven... Seven...
Seven... Seven...
Oh!
Jackpot!
Congratulations to our lucky customer,
machine number 44 just caught the fever!
Don't stop now, keep that flutter coming!
And to every life a little luck must fall!
Isn't that right, milady?
I got three sevens?
I'm getting a bad feeling here.
I have a little knowledge of Lady Tsunade
myself.
I was a member of the Medical Corps after
all.
She was the first to propose what's now a
very common practice.
For each squad to have a medical
specialist included.
Simple but brilliant.
It was a landmark idea.
What becomes of a squad
on the battlefield with
no one to administer
emergency medical treatment?
The answer is clearer than a fire in the
night.
Countless years on the
battlefield have simply
taught them how to cope
with the ravages of war.
All those who were sacrificed led to the
method you speak of.
And one only truly
grasps the value of
something once it has
been taken away from you.
This revolutionary idea, enacted by one of
the legendary Sanin, hailed for her
medical prowess, spawned in that
sacrifice.
Hey!
We're still in class here!
You foolish runt!
You guys don't have a single ounce of
concentration between the four of you!
You are all far from the path to becoming
excellent shinobi!
Sorry, but I wasn't made to sit still at a
desk.
Right, Akamaru?
[barks in agreement]
[yawn]
Man, I'm hungry.
Sensei, is this lecture almost done?
Why, you... you, you, you, you little...
From now on, you guys are staying after
school to work on your concentration!
[collective groan]
What's this for?
You're about to take up a
custom passed down through
generations of the Hidden Leaf
Village for sharpening the mind.
By concentrating all your
energy on the leaf on your
foreheads, you will learn
to build up your chakra.
It is an ancient wisdom.
By focusing on that single leaf,
nothing can distract you.
He who hones his concentration is truly a
great ninja.
This is the origin of the leaf symbol that
we wear.
Quit pulling our leg!
You sure you didn't just make that story
up to get us to work harder?
No, I'm not making it up!
It was all true!
Anyway, you can't become a great ninja
just by polishing your concentration.
Besides, everyone knows if you want to be
an awesome ninja, you gotta be strong!
He does have a point.
Stuff like this?
Catch you later, Sensei!
Hey, you boys, wait a minute!
As if!
No time, sorry!
You ungrateful little misfits!
This is the same thing.
I should have paid more attention to what
Iruka Sensei was telling us.
I'm so stupid.
Well, I guess there's no use crying over
spilled milk.
Alright, here we go.
I'm doing this no matter what!
Concentrate, concentrate...
Wow!
Tanzaku Castle sure does have a commanding
presence!
Oh, they didn't designate it a cultural
landmark for nothing, I suppose.
Stop lollygagging around.
We have to get out of this town.
But don't you want to get a better peek at
it?
It doesn't cost anything to look,
you know?
Lady Tsunade?
What is this chill I'm feeling?
This kid is something else.
The chakra was so dense it burned his
palm.
One surprise after another.
What do you know?
It finally popped.
Well done.
It looks like you've mastered the second
step.
Come on, then.
Let me hear the third one.
That'll have to wait for now.
It's time for us to meet up with Tsunade.
Isn't that..?
Orochimaru...
[evil laugh]
I finally found you.
[credits music plays]
A little pause...
and we are back.
A little pause... and we are back.